

# **ADRIAN PETROV**

Full Stack Developer

□ adrian@adrianpetrov.com

07477 139 571



## **CAREER SUMMARY**

Full Stack Developer with 4 years of non-commercial programming experience. Passionate about all things software development. Capable of solving complex problems using relevant design patterns and software development principles.

Always aspiring to produce clean, documented, DRY code. Forever a student and highly motivated, I am always tinkering with some new technology in pursuit of expanding my skillset.

I have worked with a variety of technologies, but for the last 2 years my focus has been C#/.NET Core, React and Docker.

#### **SKILLS & TOOLS**

Backend	Frontend	Others
C#/.NET Core	JavaScript/TypeScript	Git
Node.js	React	Docker
Python	Redux	AWS
Elasticsearch	Angular	Database Design
PostgreSQL/MySQL	Webpack	SOLID Principles
Entity Framework Core	HTML/CSS/SASS/LESS	

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## IT Tech Support

Aug 2018 - Present

DSM Systems is an IT Support company based in Chippenham, Wiltshire.

#### Responsibilities:

- Ensure the smooth running of services on local and cloud servers, backup systems, networking equipment.
- Ensure systems are patched up quickly after security threats are discovered.
- Deal with client queries and issues over the phone and using a ticketing system.
- Write scripts to automate frequent tasks.
- Manage users, company data, security, using Office 365 and Azure.
- Spin up and configure Lightsail/EC2 instances in AWS as and when required.
- Configure and maintain workstations (software updates, manage security threats).

#### **Business Information Administrator**

**Vallis Group** 

**DSM Systems** 

Jan 2017 - Jul 2018

Vallis Group is a logistics company operating in Africa and the Middle East with the Head Office in Frome, Somerset.

#### Responsibilities:

- Analysed and collated company data using Excel. Presented the information in formatted pivot tables for senior management and marketing purposes.
- Organised company information using MS SharePoint.
- Provided in-house IT Support to colleagues and troubleshooted IT issues before escalating with the relevant service providers.
- Updated the content on the company's WordPress website.
- Wrote and maintained the accuracy of company brochures, newsletters and presentations

### **EDUCATION**

BSc Psychology (2:1)

Bangor University 2012-2016

#### **LANGUAGES**

English (Bilingual)

Romanian (Bilingual)

#### **INTERESTS**

Strength training

Cycling

Running

Hiking and exploring

Socialising

Live music

Cooking